So let's start with bagging.
我们开始介绍bagging （自助聚集） 吧
Here's our data in the form of some red and blue points,
这是一些红蓝数据点
and for simplicity, we'll say that
为了简化
our weak learners will be the simplest possible learner.
假设我们的弱学习器用的是最简单的学习器
A Decision Tree of one-node.
单节点的决策树
So, all of them are either horizontal or a
所以 这些弱学习器要么是水平线
vertical line that says on this side everything is positive,
要么是垂直线 表示这一测都是正例
and on this side everything is negative.
而另一测都是负例
So back to our data. Let's do the following.
回到我们的数据让我们做以下的事情
Since our data may be huge,
因为数据量可能巨大
in general, we don't want to train many models on the same data.
通常 我们不想用整个数据集重复训练多个模型
This would be very expensive.
这样成本太高
Instead, we'll just take subsets of it and
相反 我们只抽取它的子集
train a weak learner on each one of these subsets.
然后用每一个子集训练弱学习器
Then we'll figure out how to combine these learners.
最后 我们再想办法把这些弱学习器组合起来
So here's our first subset of data,
这是我们的第一部分数据
and our first model,
和第一个模型
our first learner is this one.
或第一个学习器
We'll remember this one.
记住这个
Now, here's our second subset of data and our second learner.
这是第二部分数据和第二个学习器
If it looks like I'm being too lucky picking my data and my learners, yes I am.
看看我选择的数据子集和学习器  看上去我是不是太幸运了
In general these learners can be terrible,
一般来说 这些学习器可能很糟糕
but if our data is large enough,
但如果数据足够大
picking a random subset,
通过选择一个随机子集
normally gives us good intuition on the data.
通常会给我们很好的数据直觉
Plus, it makes the process run quickly.
同时会加快处理过程
Finally our third subset of data on our third learner.
最后是第三部分数据和第三个学习器
Notice that I never partition the data.
注意 我没有对数据分区
We are completely allowed to repeat points among
也就是说 我们允许重复采样 各数据子集会有重复的点
our subsets and to even not consider some of the points at all.
甚至根本不考虑某些点
At every step, we pick a fully random subset of data.
在每一步 我们都选择一个完全随机的数据子集。
Now we have three weak learners.
现在我们有三个弱学习器
How do we combine them? Well, what about voting?
如何组合它们？投票表决怎么样?
We over impose them over the data and say,
我们在数据上实行这些弱学习器
if two or more of them say blue,
如果有两个或更多判断是蓝色
then blue, and if two or more of them say red, then red.
就认为是蓝色  如果有两个或更多判断是红色  就认为是红色
If we have an even number of models,
如果我们有偶数个模型
we can pick any way we want to break ties.
我们可以选择任何希望的方式来打破联系
Although with lots of points and lots of models,
尽管有很多点和模型
it's hard to imagine that would get a tie somewhere.
但很难想象各个弱学习器之间会有依赖关系
It may happen though, and voila,
也许会发生吧
this is what we obtain when we make the models vote.
这就是我们让弱学习器们投票的结果
So that's it. That's the bagging algorithm.
就这样这就是 bagging （自助聚集）算法